{
    "subject": "resource/Exor_(company)",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Investment_company",
    "human_readable": "Exor is an investment company.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9061577916145325,
            "question": "Name some industries that Exor invests in."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8552585244178772,
            "question": "Is Exor a publicly traded company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7967569231987,
            "question": "What type of company is Exor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7172666192054749,
            "question": "Who are some major investors in Exor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5871977210044861,
            "question": "What is Exor's investment philosophy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5782933831214905,
            "question": "Does Exor primarily focus on technology investments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5145156383514404,
            "question": "Does Exor have any notable subsidiaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4044988453388214,
            "question": "Has Exor made any recent high-profile acquisitions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39631015062332153,
            "question": "What is Exor's main business objective?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3616860508918762,
            "question": "Where is Exor headquartered?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Exor is an investment company.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7111_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Exor's main business objective?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7111_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Exor made any recent high-profile acquisitions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7111_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Exor have any notable subsidiaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7111_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7111_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information supports this triple. The documents mention Exor NV as a diversified investment holding company, indicating that it is indeed an investment company."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents consistently describe Exor as an investment holding company that engages in long-term investments, manages portfolios of various companies, and operates through different investment arms such as Exor Ventures. This information supports the statement that \"Exor is an investment company.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}